SP48 is finally complete!
Yay!
Oh! It's so cool! It's got a face!
It's a selfie!
There's a selfie!
Look at the selfie! Look at it!
I'm giving away a special gift so you can make one too!
Cool!
So we have a computer and a mannitor!
Yay! Thank you! That's awesome! So, we have a computer and a mannitor. Thank you very much.
Wow, that's great.
From here, it looks like a call center.
Oh, yeah?
It's not.
I'm thinking of starting to play right away, so where do I start?
Well, first of all, I've chosen a job, and I'm going to need a shield, so I'm going to need someone to be a tank.
Yes!
That will be the shield.
That's a tank!
I'll protect you guys!
And then we need an attacker.
Yes!
Oh?
What's that?
Two attackers.
Healer.
Then I'll heal.
I'll heal you, guys.
Oh, wow.
Especially Soraha.
Soraha will be a good catch, so I'll do it
Soraha's here, too
The sound is coming
Oh, wow!
Amazing!
There's so many of them!
I thought you were the boss. This one. I thought he was a boss. Wow, they're here. There are so many of them.
Here they come. Here they come.
Wow!
Hari came out.
They look scary.
Isn't everyone here?
Wait, wait, wait.
Oh, wow.
That's great.
Wait a minute.
Somebody get out of here. This is the front. Ha ha ha
m
me
Super Imamura, where are you?
Did you hear that? I heard it.
That's great.
The other boat.
The other boat's on fire.
Is it burning?
Yeah.
It's black or something.
There's smoke.
It's real.
You attacked me.
What?
Oh, my God.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Are you attacking me?
Something black.
It's smoke.
Ally, ally, ally!
Ally, ally, black smoke.
Wow.
What is that?
Oh, my God!
We're being chased!
We're being chased.
I'll do it for you.
Oh, my God!
I got away!
I got away... and I got away... and I got away.I got away, I got away, I got away
I got away.
No.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Wait, here it comes!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, it's not working.
It's stuck.
It's not working.
That's great. 3,641 damage.
oh, my god, oh, my god, oh, my god, oh, my god, oh, my god, oh, my god, oh, my god, oh, my god, oh, my god, oh, my god.
Burned?
Oh, he's dead.
Recovery, recovery, recovery.
Something's not working.
Come on, Saayan.
I'll go help.
It's times like this when Saayan comes to our rescue.
Something's coming.
It's back, isn't it?
In 80 seconds.
Is he dead?
He's still dead.
About 70 seconds.
One minute to go.
Cinnamon Great.
They're not even looking at me when I attack.
They're not looking at me.
They've been looking at me the whole time, because I've been the closest thing Rouse has to eyes.
I'm the closest to him.
I'm alive, I'm alive, I'm alive, I'm alive, Ohhhhhh, here it comes, here it comes! Oh, no! Oh no!
It's stuck! It's stuck!
Still going!
Oh, 27!
27! That's it!
It's moving!
We can take them down now!
Oh, I think it's attacking inwards!
Oh, it's coming!
Oh, no! Oh no, oh no, oh no, oh no!
It didn't move! !!!!
I can't do it anymore
I'm dead.
Yay!
I'm dead, I can't do it anymore
I can't do it anymore
It's too hard.
Oh, no, he's dead!
I'm dead, I'm dead, I'm dead, I'm dead
I'm almost there, I'm almost there
I can do it, I can do it, I can do it, I can do it...
Oh, I'm losing.
Oh, we lost?
I think we're out of time.
Oh, no!
You're right.
Well, that's a little late for one game.
But let's change tactics.
Let's try one more time with different roles.
Yes, sir.
I want to be in recovery.
I'll be in recovery.
Recovery.
I'll be an attacker.
Then I'll be an attacker.
Look sharp.
Nice and sharp.
Yes, ma'am.
Are you okay with being the hero?
Oh, you're okay with being a hero?
Yeah, I'm good.
I'll be the attacker.
Oh, here it comes. Here it comes.
But no one's been hurt yet.
No, they're here.
It's four and five.
They're dead.
Sausage sausage sausage.Sausage sausage sausage
What are you doing?
No? What are you doing?
I'm recovering myself.
Let me recover.
We're supposed to be recovering the dead.
We're recovering ourselves.
That's too bad.
After a time, she'll go home.
She'll heal herself.
I'm here today.
Ms. Lara.
You're early.
It's early.
It'll catch on in a little while.
A little more... a little more...
I'll be there from 2:00 p.m.
I've collected the research.
It's done.
Why?
What? Okay, boo-boo, boo-boo, boo-boo, boo-boo, boo-boo... Ohhhhhhhh, everyone has experienced the game, but what do you think? No, it was great!
It was fun!
It was so much fun!
It was a little difficult at first,
It was a little difficult at first, but we knew it would only take a few days at a time,
The four of us, we were more united,
We had to find jobs that fit as well as we could.
When will the game be released?
Yes, we are working on it.
What is the information about the release of the game?
BANPIC GAMES and
SKY-FOOLING's official Twitter.
We will be releasing more information,
Please follow us.
Thank you very much.
The game itself will be
The game itself will be released in the summer/fall,
I hope you will all give it a try,
I hope you will all give it a try, and I hope you will wait for AQ4 as well.
Please wait for us.
We are waiting for you.
I would like to do it.
Thank you very much.
It was fun~.
If you find this video interesting, please give it a high rating and subscribe to our channel.
Watch the next video too!